<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on My projects</title>
    <link>https://pages.recursive.me/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on My projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:34:28 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pages.recursive.me/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hascard</title>
      <link>https://pages.recursive.me/projects/hascard/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2020 11:34:28 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pages.recursive.me/projects/hascard/</guid>
      <description>Hascard is a minimal commandline utility for reviewing notes. &amp;lsquo;Flashcards&amp;rsquo; can be written in markdown-like syntax. Check the README for more info. I made this to improve my Haskell skills and also thought this would be somewhat useful to me if I managed to finish it. I did struggle a bit, especially the rendering of the open questions was a pain, but in the end I finished it and I am happy with how it turned out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Park</title>
      <link>https://pages.recursive.me/projects/park/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pages.recursive.me/projects/park/</guid>
      <description>This is a collection of algorithmic botany sketches in the form of a website. I improved my HTML/CSS/JavaScript skills a bit, and also learned a little about templating and buildtools by working with gulp and nunjucks. I think I spent most of my time working on the tree on the homepage, it&amp;rsquo;s calculated via the 3D space colonization algorithm and rendered with THREE.js. Apart from that, the leaf venation and L-system sketches are my favorites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Garden</title>
      <link>https://pages.recursive.me/projects/garden/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pages.recursive.me/projects/garden/</guid>
      <description>The idea of this project was to make a collection of all sorts of trees. I did not make as many trees as I wanted initially and it&amp;rsquo;s all very simple, but it was still a fun exercise. Two sketches were made with p5.js, the binary tree with d3.js, and the minimal spanning tree was done with sigma.js.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>